Guide to the John Taber papers, 1880-1965.
Taber, John papers
- Subject Files, 1923-1958
  - Civil Service Employment, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Civil Service General, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Civil Service Retirement, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Civil Service State Department Blanks, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Commerce Department, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Condolences, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Congress Street Corporation, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Congress Street Corporation, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Congressional Record, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Cornell University, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence Quarterly, 1956 (Box 36)
  - DCW, 1956 (Box 21)
  - DCW, 1956 (Box 22)
  - DCW Deposit Slips, 1956 (Box 22)
  - DCW Receipts, 1956 (Box 22)
  - DCW Receipts, 1956 (Box 21)
  - DCW slips, 1958, 1956 (Box 22)
  - DCW Washington (envelope), 1956 (Box 22)
  - Deposit Slips, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Dorothy C. Whitehouse, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Dorothy C. Whitehouse Receipts, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Envelope - Birthday Letters, JT, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Flood Control, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Flood Control Area - Cortland Area and Monash Point, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Flood Control Area - Great Modus Bay, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Flood Control Area - Locke, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Flood Control Area - Moravia, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Flood Control Area - Port Bay, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Flood Control Area - Schuyler County, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Flood Control Area - Modus Bay, Charles Point, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Flood Control Area - Modus Swamp, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Football Tickets, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Foreign Claims Supplement, 1956 (Box 30)
  - General Accounting, 1956 (Box 30)
  - General Campaign, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Government Printing Office, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Hart Manufacturing, Phelps, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Immigration, 1956 (Box 27)
    1956 and prior
  - Internal Revenue, 1956 (Box 36)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Invitations accepted, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Invitations declined, 1956 (Box 36)
  - JT Campaign, 1956 (Box 30)
  - JT Personal, 1956 (Box 21)
  - JT Receipts, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Judiciary, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Justice, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Liaison Officers, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Library of Congress, 1956 (Box 36)
  - M. D. Higgins Report, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Mahoning, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Maple Grove Apartments, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Marsh Creek, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Middle East, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Milk Production, New York State, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 36)
  - N.Y. State, 1956 (Box 30)
  - N.Y.S. Republican Commission, 1956 (Box 29)
  - New C.I.A. Buildings, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Pearce, Alfred, Internal Revenue, 1956 (Box 36)
  - Plymouth, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Primary thanks, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Sampson - Proposed Disposal, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Sampson Air Base, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Sampson Incoming Correspondence, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Sampson Incoming Correspondence, 1956 (Box 29)
  - School Trips, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Second Supplement, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Selective Services, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Seneca Ordinance, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Sergeant at Arms, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Small Business Administration, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Social Security, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Soil Conservation, 1956 (Box 29)
  - State Department, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Stationary, Telephone, Telegraph, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Stationary, Telephone, Telegraph, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Stock Reports, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Stock Reports, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Stock Reports, 1956 (Box 22)
  - T. W. Case Estate, 1956 (Box 22)
  - T. W. Case Estate (miscellaneous letters), 1956 (Box 22)
  - Taber - receipts, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Taber - receipts, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Taber - receipts, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Tariff, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Taxes, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Ted Case Estate, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Telephone, Telegraph, etc., 1956 (Box 21)
  - U.S. Information Agencies, 1956 (Box 29)
  - United Nations, 1956 (Box 29)
  - UNTA, 1956 (Box 29)
  - WCW, 1956 (Box 21)
  - WCW, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Willard C. Whitehouse, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Year Book of Agriculture, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Year Book of Agriculture, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Young Republicans, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Acknowledgements, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Agricultural Year Books, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Agriculture, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Agriculture, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Agriculture, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Agriculture, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Agriculture Onions, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Agriculture Potatoes, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Agriculture Soil Bank, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Appointments, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Appreciations to JT, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Army and Navy Games, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Army Matters, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Atomic Power Plant, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Auburn, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Birthday, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Bureau of the Budget, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Campaign, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Capitol, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Civil Defense, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Civil Service Employment, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Civil Service General, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Civil Service Retirement, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Commerce Department, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Condolences, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Congressional Directory, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Congressional Quarterly, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Congressional Record, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Cornell University, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Corps of Engineers, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Defense Department, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Federal Housing Administration, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Flood Control, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Flood Control Legislation, 1957 (Box 27)
  - Football tickets, 1957 (Box 24)
  - General Accounting, 1957 (Box 24)
  - General Services, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Government Printing Office, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Hoover Commission, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Housing, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Inauguration, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Interior Department, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Internal Revenue, 1957 (Box 24)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Invitations Accepted, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Invitations Declined, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Johnson City Flood Walls, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Joint Congressional Committee on Atomic Energy, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Judgeships, 1957 (Box 27)
  - Justice, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Labor Department, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Liaison Officers, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Library of Congress, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Lotito, Luca, 1957 (Box 27)
  - Mahoning, 1957 (Box 22)
  - Milk Marketing, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Milk Producers of N.Y.S., 1957 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Mohawk Airlines, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Mrs. Joyce Annie Fuller, 1957 (Box 27)
  - N.Y. National Guard, 1957 (Box 25)
  - N.Y. Representative Committee, 1957 (Box 25)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, 1957 (Box 25)
  - National Association of Independent Voters, 1957 (Box 25)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Newsletters, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Passports, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Post Office Department, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Private Bills, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Radio and Television, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Reclamation, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Recommendations, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Referrals, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Refugee Relief Programs, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Remington Corporation, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Republican Whip, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Reservations, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Route 12, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Route 13, Ludlowville, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Rural Route Extension Forms, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Sampson Air Base, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Selective Service, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Seneca Ordinance, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Small Business Administration, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Social Security, 1957 (Box 26)
  - State Department, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Statements, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Stewart Air Force Base - Newburgh, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Three folder entitled, A-F, G-O, P-Z, followed by other correspondence in brown folders, A-Z, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Tours, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Treasury Department, 1957 (Box 26)
  - U.S. Information Agency, 1957 (Box 26)
  - United Nations, 1957 (Box 26)
  - Washington Correspondence, 1957 (Box 26)
  - WHEN Radio, Norwich, 1957 (Box 25)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Hold for JT's attention, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Hoover Commission, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Housing, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Inflation, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Integration, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Interior Department, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Internal Revenue, 1958 (Box 15)
  - International Cooperative Administration, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Invitations Accepted, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Invitations Declined, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Judiciary, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Justice Department, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Labor Department, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Library of Congress, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Middle East Situation, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 15)
  - N.Y. Republican Delegation, 1958 (Box 16)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, 1958 (Box 16)
  - N.Y.S. Roads, 1958 (Box 16)
  - National Federation of Independent Voters, 1958 (Box 15)
  - NATO, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Newsletter, 1958 (Box 16)
  - NLRB, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Passports, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Photographs, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Pleasant Valley, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Post Office Department, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Private Bills, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Publication, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Radio and Television, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Reciprocal Trade, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Recommendations, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Referrals, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Republican National Committee, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Seneca Ordinance, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Small Business Administration, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Social Security, 1958 (Box 16)
  - State Department, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Statements made by Mr. Taber, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Tariff Commission, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Taxes, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Tours, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Treasury Department, 1958 (Box 16)
  - U.S. Information Agency, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Unemployment, 1958 (Box 16)
  - United Nations, 1958 (Box 16)
  - White House, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Wickwire Employer Letters, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Young Republicans, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Cayuga County, Date Unknown (Box 125)
  - Chenango County, Date Unknown (Box 125)
  - Cortland County, Date Unknown (Box 125)
  - Ontario County, Date Unknown (Box 125)
  - Schuyler County, Date Unknown (Box 125)
  - Seneca County, Date Unknown (Box 125)
  - Tompkins County, Date Unknown (Box 125)
  - Yates County, Date Unknown (Box 125)
- Assorted Files, 1931-1957
  - Aunt Sammy's Radio Recipe, 1931 (Box 132)
  - Howard M. Thomas, 1935-1937 (Box 162)
  - Report No. 4 for Second Quarter, 1937 (Box 91)
  - Old Age Pensions, Welfare Act, 1938 (Box 94)
  - New Trade Agreement with Canada, 1938-11-17 (Box 91)
  - Trade Agreement with United Kingdom, 1938-11-17 (Box 91)
  - Statistics of Capital Movements Between U.S. and Foreign Countries, 1938-12 (Box 91)
  - Six Hearings, Extension of Reciprocal Trade Agreement Act, Vol 1, 1940 (Box 91)
  - The Bond Survey, 1941 (Box 132)
  - "Report to the President of the United States, Funds and Operations, 1935-42," pamphlet, 1942 (Box 69)
  - West Point, 1943 (Box 69)
  - Veterans Cases (alphabetical), 1944-1949 (Box 101)
  - Ways and Means, 1944-1945 (Box 127)
  - "R.F.C. Mr. Taber", 1945 (Box 96)
  - Military Affairs, 1945 (Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1945 (Box 94)
  - O.P.A., 1945 (Box 96)
  - O.P.A. Gasoline, 1945 (Box 95)
  - O.P.A. General, 1945 (Box 95)
  - O.P.A. Rent Control, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Office Price Administration, 1945 (Box 96)
  - P.W.A., 1945 (Box 96)
  - Panama, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Passport, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Patents, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Petroleum Administrations, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Price Control, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Priority, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Procurement, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Public Works Administration, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Publications, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Publications, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Puerto Rico, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Pulteneyville Harbor, 1945 (Box 95)
  - Pulteneyville Harbor, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Questionnaires, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Republican County Commission, 36th District, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Republican Party, 1945 (Box 96)
  - Washington Office, 1946 (Box 156)
  - Agriculture and Forestry in East Oderland (East Pomerania, East Brandenburg, Border Province), 1947 (Box 132)
  - Agriculture, Stock Farming, Forestry in Silesia, 1947 (Box 132)
  - Alphabetical File through 1947, 1947 (Box 156)
  - Hearings on Social Security Vol. 1, 1947-1955 (Box 94)
  - Hearings on Social Security Vol. 3, 1947-1955 (Box 94)
  - Incoming Mail, 1947-1948 (Box 94)
  - Printed Manual of Practical Political Action, 1947-1955 (Box 94)
  - Black Scrapbook of Newspaper Clippings, 1948 (Box 162)
  - Miscellaneous printed matter, newspaper clippings and photographs, 1948 (Box 169)
  - Armed Services, 1949 (Box 134)
  - Judiciary, 1949 (Box 135)
  - Labor, 1949 (Box 135)
  - Ways and Means, 1949 (Box 135)
  - Agriculture, 1950 (Box 133)
  - Flood Control, 38th District, 1950-1954 (Box 101)
  - Auburn (N.Y.) Veterans, 1951 (Box 102)
  - Veterans (General), 1951 (Box 102)
  - Campaign, 1952 (Box 69)
  - Chenango County Flood Control, 1952-1953 (Box 101)
  - Civil Service and Retirement, 1952 (Box 120)
  - Displaced Persons, 1952 (Box 102)
  - C. K. Reports, 1953 (Box 69)
  - Post Office, 1953 (Box 102)
  - Refugee Relief, 1953-1956 (Box 102)
  - Civil Functions and Military Construction, 1954 (Box 162)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (alphabetical), 1954 (Box 102)
  - Treasury - Post Office, 1954 (Box 162)
  - White House, 1954 (Box 162)
  - Air Force, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Amendments to Appropriation Bills, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Apples Appropriation, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Appropriation, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Army, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Army and Navy, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Auburn, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Budget, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Cayuga County, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Civil Service and Employment, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Clippings, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Commerce Department, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Condolences, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Cortland County, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Department of Agriculture and Related Agencies, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Department of Commerce, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Department of Defense, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare and Related, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Department of Interior and Related, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Department of State and Justice, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Department of the Treasury, 1955 (Box 32)
  - District of Columbia, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Foreign Aid, 1955 (Box 32)
  - General Government Matters, 1955 (Box 32)
  - House Bills, 1955 (Box 31)
  - Housing, Civil Defense, and other, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Independent Offices, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Investigative Staff, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Invitations, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Janet Hill Gordon, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Judiciary, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Labor, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Legislative, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Legislative, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Marine Corps, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Mohawk Airlines, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Navy Department, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Public Works, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Senate Bills, 1955 (Box 31)
  - Agriculture, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Banking and Currency, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Bills and Resolution, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Civil Service, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Congressional Committee, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Corps of Engineers, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Department of Defense, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Department of Defense, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Dixon Yates, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Envelope - Business Machines, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Envelope - News Releases and Statements made by Donahue, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Envelope - Sampson Newspaper Clippings, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Farm Bill H.R. 10875, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Federal Commission, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Files, 1956, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Fish and Wild Life, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Flood Control, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Highway, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Hold for Mr. Taber, 1956 (Box 33)
  - Hold for Mr. Taber's attention, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Housing, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Immigration, 1956 (Box 33)
  - Interior Department, 1956 (Box 33)
  - Interior Department, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Judiciary, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Kelly Bill - Federal Aid for Schools, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Labor, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Legislative Daily, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Legislative HEW, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Mailing List, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 165)
  - Mitchell Sampson, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Mount Valley Water Company, 1956 (Box 31)
  - N.L.R.H., 1956 (Box 31)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, 1956 (Box 31)
  - N.Y.S. Republican Delegation, 1956 (Box 31)
  - National Convention, 1956 (Box 31)
  - National Federation of Independent Voters, 1956 (Box 31)
  - National Insurance of Manufacturers, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Newsletters, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Newspapers, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Number of folders on Post Office through 1956, General Appropriations, Government Operations, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Office of the Clerk, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Paperwork Management, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Passports, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Patronage [empty], 1956 (Box 31)
  - Pending Publications, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Penfield Manufacturing Company, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Phone calls, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Post Office Department, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Private bills, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Public Works, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Publications, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Publicity, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Radio and Television, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Recommendations, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Referrals, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Refugee Relief Program, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Remington Corporation, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Republican Whip, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Sampson - Congressional Air Force, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Sampson (incoming correspondence), 1956 (Box 35)
  - Sampson Air Base, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Sampson Geneva Times, 1956 (Box 35)
  - Social Security, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Statements of Mr. Taber, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Statements of Mr. Taber, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Upper Colorado River Project, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Veterans, 1956 (Box 34)
  - Ways and Means, 1956 (Box 31)
  - WCHN Radio, Norwich, 1956 (Box 35)
  - White House, 1956 (Box 31)
  - "Townsend Plan Figures", Date Unknown (Box 93)
  - A Year of Potsdam, Date Unknown (Box 132)
  - Agriculture, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Agriculture and Forestry, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Alphabetical file of Estate Tax Clients, Date Unknown (Box 177)
  - Alphabetical file of Estate Tax Waivers, A - G, I - R, T (H and S missing), Date Unknown (Box 178)
  - Alphabetical file of Estate Tax Waivers, U, V, XYZ (and many without folders, may be the missing letters), Date Unknown (Box 179)
  - Appointments, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Appropriations, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Appropriations, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Appropriations - Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - Appropriations Federal Budget, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - Banking and Currency, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Banking and Currency, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Banking and Currency, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Budget, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Capital, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Cayuga Campers Records and misc. printed items, pamphlets, and news clippings., Date Unknown (Box 182)
  - Cayuga County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Chenango County, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Civil Aeronautics Administration, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Civil Rights, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Civil Service, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Civil Service and Employment, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Coast Guard, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Commerce Department, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Condolences, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Congressional, Date Unknown (Box 156)
  - Congressional Directory, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Congressional Record, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Coordinator of Information, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Copies of VICTORY and other publications., Date Unknown (Box 79)
  - Cortland County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Department of Defense, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - District of Columbia, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Economic Stabilization Agency, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Education, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Education, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Employment, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Envelope - Foreign and Domestic Committee, Date Unknown (Box 92)
  - Envelopes containing samples of German, British, and American propaganda., Date Unknown (Box 79)
  - European Aid, General, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Expenditures in Executive Departments, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Expenditures in the Executive Department - legislative, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Farm Bulletins, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Federal Bids, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Federal Civil Defense Administrations, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Federal Communications Commission, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Federal Security Agency, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Fish and Wild Life, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Fish and Wildlife Service, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Football, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Foreign Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Foreign Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - General Accounting Office, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - General Services and Administration, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Hawaii and Alaska, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Hoover Commission, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Hoover Commission (Organization of Executive Branch of the Government, Committee on), Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Housing, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Housing, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Housing, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Interior Department, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - John Foster Dulles, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Judiciary, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Labor, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Labor, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Langer Bill, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Large envelopes of correspondence for and against European Relief (E.R.P.), Date Unknown (Box 93)
  - Large folder containing material on Trade Agreements, Date Unknown (Box 92)
  - Large folder containing miscellaneous correspondence and printed matter, Date Unknown (Box 91)
  - Larry's File, Date Unknown (Box 156)
  - Legislation, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Legislative Sub-Committee, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - Lend-Lease, Date Unknown (Box 135)
  - Lend-Lease material, Date Unknown (Box 78)
  - Lend-Lease material, Date Unknown (Box 79)
  - Loyalty Check, Date Unknown (Box 135)
  - Medicine, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Medicine, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Military Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence re Appropriations Civil Functions, Date Unknown (Box 162)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 156)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, Date Unknown (Box 127)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Miscellaneous matter on Reciprocal Trade Agreements, Date Unknown (Box 92)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 131)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Matter, Date Unknown (Box 91)
  - Mr. Taber, Date Unknown (Box 165)
  - National Defense, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - National Defense, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - National Federation of Independent Business, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - National Federation of Small Business, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - National Science Foundation, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Navy Ordnance Department, Date Unknown (Box 162)
  - Norman cousins, Date Unknown (Box 135)
  - Office of Education, Date Unknown (Box 120)
  - Office of War Information, Mr. Taber's attacks, Date Unknown (Box 78)
  - Office of War Information, Mr. Taber's attacks, Date Unknown (Box 79)
  - Pending, Date Unknown (Box 156)
  - Post Office, Date Unknown (Box 133)
  - Post Office, Date Unknown (Box 134)
  - Post Office and Post Roads, Date Unknown (Box 127)